Closed Captional made
by the No part of the
video is available on the right or wrong.
No
part
of
the video
is available on now,
is the only way to Newsom.
Back to the video.
The first time we can
get a new conversation,
the rest is being in the
right or wrong. Aliens,
the other part is a feature
of the universe and the
reality of the universe and
the reality of the universe.
You know, you may be a person
and your view of the universe,
but you can see the universe.
Every time we present theon by Deep,
you can see the world as a writer.
I could boast about how my
injury was earned in battle,
but I take no pride in how that battle
transpired.
My right hand is getting
better, but it'll take time.
While the intermediate phalanx of
my little finger is merely cracked,
in my middle and ring fingers,
the fourth and fifth metacarpals
and proximal phalanges are completely
fractured and will take four weeks to heal.
For once, I honestly regret the
actions I took during this incident.
It's clear that this stemmed from a fault
in my personality.
I crossed a red line that wasn't meant
to be crossed, stuck my nose into
someone else's business.
I prided myself on being able to see
the truth of a person's character.
Now I know I was foolish.
Everything above my wrist is intact,
only thanks to a stroke of
pure blind luck that day.
Thank you.
An hour and a half ride on the Shinkansen
will take you from S-City Station,
southwest of the town of
Morioh, to Tokyo Station.
From there, another Monday train
ride will take you to Harajuku.
Yoma Hashimoto had just
taken that very trip
when he was scouted by
a woman from a modeling
and production agency.
In turn, his photos appeared in
magazines and he landed a minor
role in a film.
While on set, he even caught a
distant glimpse of the leading man.
And And it reminded him of what his
agent said to him at the very beginning.
You know what makes an
actor or a model a star?
They can draw you in with their
aura, even if they're standing still.
That comes from training your body.
Talent has nothing on a body that
makes every stance a beautiful pose.
Feeling as bright and
energetic as the sun overhead,
Yoma Hashimoto began the
best days of his life.
one last set you got this three
two two
two still
two one last one
Okay, that's it. Perfection.
Sure, I might have lied about the rep
counts, but lying's just what I do.
And you made it through a
whole week of my training.
See the way your veins
are bulging out over here?
Absolutely beautiful.
Let's go.
Dinner's ready! Yoma!
Ow!
Could you not leave your
weights lying around?
Are you seriously jumping rope inside?
Yeah, sorry.
I'll put him away.
Gotta say, your routine's really working.
I mean, your abs are looking spectacular.
You look like...
Oh, I know!
Like Brad Pitt in Fight Club! Oh?
You're amazing!
Who knew it was possible
to get so jacked that fast?
But wow!
If you were the star
of a detective movie...
You'd be fantastic!
Oh, by the way, the cod
roast spaghetti's ready!
Let's eat it while it's hot!
Uh, spaghetti?
Yeah!
Didn't I tell you before, Mika?
I'm not eating carbs or fats. Huh?
I only eat protein.
It's better for developing
muscles than all that other crap.
This is my menu.
I expect you to stick to it.
Is this all you're going to eat now?
But what about tonight when we go
out for drinks with all our friends?
Well, I won't be going to that.
I'm running 10k at 4am tomorrow.
I'm off to bed. Bed?
But it's only 7 o 'clock in the evening.
Wait, there's no money in my wallet.
Oh, right.
I forgot to tell you.
My gym was having a special
deal on protein powder.
2,000 grams or 4,800.
Chocolate flavored, too. Super cheap.
Definitely cheaper than the cod roe.
So I borrowed 5,000 yen.
Sorry.
I'll give you the money back tomorrow.
What?
Alright, I gotta shower and sleep.
You should probably go home now.
But Yoma, this is my apartment!
Hmm?
Oh, is that right?
I guess it is.
Hey!
How many damn times do you
have to ring that bell?
I told you before.
Enough with the evening deliveries!
Yoma!
I'm trying to sleep here.
Calm down!
If you wake me up one more
time, I'll beat your ass!
Sorry about that.
It all began with idle gym talk.
Conversations like, you start burning
fat after 15 minutes of running.
So you should warm up with a
Monday run on the treadmill.
Things like that.
That's how we started talking.
Rohan-sensei, it looks
like you're in top shape.
Those waists don't stand
a chance against you.
Go!
Wow, looking good.
Oh, oh my God.
Nice work.
That was fun.
Always nice to have a little competition.
Hey, Coach.
Should I breathe in?
Or should I breathe out here? Sorry, bud.
Can't help you.
This gentleman here signed up for
a personal training session today,
okay, you ready to go?
Work those out your muscles will
love it if you just talk to him?
The final set one two three!
You know I've asked you not to jump
rope in here over and over have
you I have and I told you not To
leave your training stuff all over the
place remember is that right but I
used this stuff Clearly look at how
gross the floor is stop what you
careful now let's not get too close
Almost there six seven eight nine ten!
What are you doing?
Isn't it obvious? Bouldering.
Bouldering.
You cemented a handhold
right over our thermostat.
Oh, did I?
Well, we don't really
need it anymore, do we?
That air conditioner was taking up space.
Once we're rid of it, maybe I'll
set up a Polpo machine there.
Could you please come down and talk to me?
It's about my debit card.
You took it out of my handbag, didn't you?
Give it back!
Pretty sure I put it back in there.
No!
I mean the money you took!
You spent 270,000 yen without even asking!
What'd you even spend it on?
I'll pay you back when I
land my next film roll.
I can't deal with you anymore.
How did you even know my PIN number?
It's his birthday.
Your exes you need to get out
of my apartment right now.
I'll call the police.
You're not serious!
Are you you asshole get the hell out
of here all right then if you want me to
This place it's a rental
you're completely insane.
Two treadmills of the same make and model.
The speed increases automatically and can
reach a maximum of 25 kilometers per hour.
Usain Bolt runs 100 meters at
35 to 37 kilometers per hour.
Faster than I could ever dream of, but
this machine runs speeds of up to 25 kph.
You up for a rematch?
Or so I asked him.
There was only one
remote for both machines.
That's how we were set up.
We were running at 13.2
kph and kept speeding
up until we reached 25
kilometers per hour.
Then whoever snatched the
remote and pressed the
emergency stop button
first would be the winner.
By the way, to keep it
fair, we need a judge.
Think a coach could help out?
It's like my personal training client
dropped off the face of the earth.
It's been two whole weeks
since I've even heard from him.
What should I do?
I haven't had any luck
trying to contact him either.
Same rule as his last time worked for you?
Remember, touch the remote
before 25 kph and you lose.
Hey now, what's with
the look? Hold on a sec.
You're not playing around, huh?
I see.
Still holding a grudge
from our previous run.
Same rule as his last time then?
Oh yeah, you told me you
were an actor and a model.
How's work been treating you lately?
Rohan sensei, I recommend you
focus entirely on your running.
I've accepted your challenge.
The competition has begun.
This won't play out like before.
This time I'm gonna whip your scrawny ass.
Rohan Kishibe
What the hell?
17.2 kilometers per hour
Your body, it didn't look like that last
time Your name is Yomahashimoto, right?
You're 21, aren't you?
Amazing Your sides.
How did you build all that muscle?
Those serratus anteriors,
that's no mere six pack.
Your muscle definition's
beyond anything I've ever seen.
Your serratus anteriors are incredible.
Just shut up and run.
I've passed 18k per hour.
What?
The shape of his muscles?
Those can't be!
19k per hour.
Rohan-sensei,
during our last race, you sneakily
struck that table with your fingers.
It knocked the remote over in a
way that gave you an unfair edge.
You caused the remote
to fall into your hand.
It seems the scales were unbalanced.
Not a true match.
A competition should not be ambiguous.
It's not gonna fly this time around.
Wait a minute now.
We're just playing a game here.
Yeah.
Yeah, a little game between
two buddies at the gym.
Just playing around.
But if you're not playing fair,
there's no way to name a winner.
It's even truer for a rematch.
We have to make sure
everything is done right.
Revenge is only worth it
when it's taken fairly.
All of this because you
couldn't grab the remote?
Are you saying that I'm
a cheater or something?
I'm just saying our game is gonna be fair.
What the?
the hell is he doing? Backwards?
He's running backwards
on a treadmill at 20
kilometers per hour? How?
What incredible athleticism. What?
What's he up to?
Why is
he running backwards?
Hey, what on earth are you?
20.2k per hour.
Now 20.4!
Hold on.
Did you?
Competition's lurking behind
every aspect of our lives.
That's why fairness is so vital.
If you live without fairness,
there's no way you can ever improve.
Now it's fair.
Whoever takes the remote first will
win a perfect, indisputable victory.
We're coming to the hard
part now. Rohan Kishive!
Who the hell are you?
What are you?
I'm at 21.4K.
Oh, it's a little too early for that.
Like you said, we can't press the
stop button until we reach 25 kph.
What if I should grab the remote first?
I left you two fingers
to press the button.
That is fairness.
So neither one of us can
hold a grudge when it's over.
The entire point of a rematch is to
decide the true winner, isn't it?
What the...
Heaven's Door.
Yoma, what have you...
This man, this Yomohashi Mode is...
Dammit, stop!
Now we're up to 23K.
You better not fall yet, Rohan-sensei.
23.3 kilometers per hour.
23.7.
24K now.
Shit.
Goddammit.
This is bad. Really bad.
If I don't get that remote
before he does, I'm dead.
I won!
I beat you!
I went for it with everything I had.
Make no mistake, your movements were
quicker and more elegant than mine.
This victory is indisputably yours.
Too bad for you, I've got heaven's door.
The power to make someone into
a book and rewrite them too.
Just now, I took the
chance to write in you.
But as far as our competition's
concerned, you've won.
I concede. Isn't that enough?
You were the one who
ultimately pressed the button.
Rohan.
I'm not going to look down through this
broken window, to the scene down below.
Even if I did, I'm sure I
wouldn't see Yoma at the bottom.
He may be clinging to the side
of the building somewhere.
I need to get out of
this place immediately.
I need to escape.
Though I didn't intend to,
I'd crossed the red line.
If I looked out of this window now,
if I stuck my head out as if to look
down upon him, he would probably kill me.
The muscles on his back
were in the shape of wings.
The ones above his ankles, too.
And when the wind blew through his
hair, I saw them behind his ears.
They were a symbol, I'm sure of it.
He's a man possessed.
The wings were the sign.
He is possessed by the God of Muscle.
This god has many names.
In Greek myth, he is called Hermes.
Yoma Hashimoto has turned
into the god Hermes incarnate.
I shouldn't have gone anywhere near him.
I risked my life in our
competition for that remote.
That's the truth.
but that still doesn't
mean he'll ever accept it.
I sincerely hope I haven't
brought his wrath down on me.
The only thing I can do now is run.
I want to know the truth
of life that never melts.
To chain a mystic rise, I'm coming!
I'm on my way to find eternal reality.
I can feel my heart beating.
I can see my faith.
All spinning round?
Beyond the time!
Rise up to the sky.
Like a butterfly.
Show me what's inside.
All the sights over the world go.
Shining stars will guide me to
Somewhere high finding the truth?
Beyond the heaven's door.
Thank you.